<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://aivillage.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aivillage.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DEFCON 26 Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/events/vegas2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/events/vegas2018/</guid>
      <description>The AI Village at DEFCON is a place where experts in AI and security (or both!) can come together to learn and discuss the use, and misuse, of artificial intelligence in traditional security. Artificial Learning techniques are rapidly being deployed in core security technologies like malware detection and network traffic analysis, but their use has also opened up a variety of new attack vectors against the systems that use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Village Panel Announcement</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/panel-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/posts/panel-announcement/</guid>
      <description>With DEF CON just two months away, we&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce two panels that will be held at AI Village this year! Here&amp;rsquo;s what we have planned for attendees so far:
##(Responsible?) Offensive Machine Learning
Panelists @_delta_zero (Moderating) @bodeaceacat @Straithe @filar
Abstract: Cool evil hacks using machine learning are exploding in popularity. Not all ML abuse looks like Terminators, but also DeepFakes, political impersonation, and distracting autonomous cars.
What does &amp;ldquo;Max Evil&amp;rdquo; in machine learning look like, really?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DEFCON China BETA 2018</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/events/china2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/events/china2018/</guid>
      <description>Time 12 May (Sat) 13 May (Sun)     1000 Village Exhibits Machine Learning as a Tool for Societal Exploitation: A Summary on the Current and Future State of Affairs - F1F1cin   1100 StuxNNet: Practical Live Memory Attacks on Machine Learning Systems - Raphael Norwitz Scrutinizing the Weakness and Strength of AI Systems - Dr Xinyu Xing, Dr Jimmy Su, Wenbo Guo   1200 Machine learning model hardening for fun and profit - Ariel Herbert-Voss StuxNNet: Practical Live Memory Attacks on Machine Learning Systems - Raphael Norwitz   1300 AI vs AI: Undercover the Billions of Black Market in e-Commerce - Dr Bin Zhao, Jin Yang Facilitating Postmortem Program Analysis with Deep Learning - Dr Xinyu Xing, Dr Jimmy Su, Wenbo Guo   1400 WORKSHOP: Pwning Machine Learning Systems - Clarence Chio Closing   1700 Village Exhibits -    Abstracts StuxNNet: Practical Live Memory Attacks on Machine Learning Systems slides, video 1, video 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dimensionality and Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/dimensionality-and-adversarial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/posts/dimensionality-and-adversarial/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to AI Village’s series on adversarial examples. This will focus on image classification attacks as they are simpler to work with and this series is meant to explain the attacks to hackers who have an interest in data science. The underlying principles are the same for attacks against malware/spam/security classifiers, though the implementation varies. This post focuses on the core reason why adversarial examples work, the high dimensional space our data occupies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the AI Village</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/about/</guid>
      <description>The AI Village is a community of hackers and data scientists working to educate the world on the use and abuse of artificial intelligence in security and privacy.
We are not sponsored by any one company, and it is our mission to maintain it as such as the community grows.
We have a presence at DEF CON, the world&amp;rsquo;s longest running and largest underground hacking conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>All delegates, speakers, sponsors and volunteers at AI Village are required to agree with the following code of conduct. Organizers will enforce this code throughout the event.
THE SHORT VERSION AI Village is dedicated to providing a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of participants in any form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/sponsors/</guid>
      <description> Our sponsors make this all possible!
If you or your company is interested to be a sponsor, please get in touch with us.
Gold Sponsors  &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEAM</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/team/</guid>
      <description> Join us on our Slack channel (invitation)
CFP Review Board  @ak1010 @alexcpsec @filar @gradient_janitor @phtully @redragonvn @SaraTerp @Straithe @DavidFreeman  Core  @_delta_zero @adversariel @bwall @cchio @comath @filar @lysine_chan  Speakers DEFCON CHINA BETA (11-13 May 2018)  @adversariel @BinZhao @cchio @F1F1cin @raphael_norwitz @WenboGuo  Team  @antojosep007 @dth0m @eugeneteo @grue_ @J_L_Igyarto @rseymour  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>