<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://aivillage.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aivillage.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DEFCON 26 Las Vegas</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/events/vegas2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/events/vegas2018/</guid>
      <description>The AI Village at DEFCON is a place where experts in AI and security (or both!) can come together to learn and discuss the use, and misuse, of artificial intelligence in traditional security. Artificial Learning techniques are rapidly being deployed in core security technologies like malware detection and network traffic analysis, but their use has also opened up a variety of new attack vectors against the systems that use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Village Accepted Talks</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/accepted-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/posts/accepted-talks/</guid>
      <description>DEF CON 26 is only one month away! We have a large number of amazing talks planned for everyone in attendance:
Full List    Title Speaker Type     The current state of adversarial machine learning infosecanon Presentation   StuxNNet: Practical Live Memory Attacks on Machine Learning Systems Raphael Norwitz Presentation   Holy BATSense! Deploying TBATS Machine Learning Algorithm to Detect Security Events Pranshu Bajpai Presentation   Machine Learning for Network Security Hands-on Workshop: DIYML Sebastian Garcia Workshop   Detecting Web Attacks with Recurrent Neural Networks Fedor Sakharov Presentation   Using AI to Create Music dj beep code Exhibit   It’s a Beautiful Day in the Malware Neighborhood Matt Presentation   IntelliAV: Building an Effective On-Device Android Malware Detector Mansour Ahmadi Presentation   Chatting with your programs to find vulnerabilities Chris Gardner Presentation   Hunting the Ethereum Smart Contract: Color-inspired Inspection of Potential Attacks TonTon Huang Presentation   Deep Exploit Isao Takaesu Exhibit   Beyond Adversarial Learning &amp;ndash; Security Risks in AI Implementations Kang Li Presentation   DeepPhish: Simulating the Malicious Use of AI Ivan Torroledo Presentation   AI DevOps: Behind the Scenes of a Global Anti-Virus Company&amp;rsquo;s Machine Learning Infrastructure Alex Long Presentation   Generating Labeled Data From Adversary Simulations With MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Brian Genz Presentation   JMPgate: Accelerating reverse engineering into hyperspace using AI Rob Brandon Presentation   Automated Planning for the Automated Red Team Andy Applebaum Presentation   Stop and Step Away from the Data: Rapid Anomaly Detection via Ransom Note File Classification Mark Mager Presentation   Identifying and correlating anomalies in Internet-wide scan traffic to newsworthy security events Andrew Morris Presentation   Machine Learning Model Hardening For Fun and Profit Ariel Herbert-Voss Presentation   The great power of AI: Algorithmic mirrors of society Aylin Caliskan Presentation   GAN to the dark side: A case study of attacking machine-learning systems to empower defenses Li Chen Presentation   Towards a framework to quantitatively assess AI safety – challenges, open questions and opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Attacks</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/optimization-fgsm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/posts/optimization-fgsm/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the second post in the AI Village&amp;rsquo;s adversarial machine learning series. This one will cover the greedy fast methods that are most commonly used. We will explain what greedy means and why certain choices were made that may not be obvious to newcomers. This is meant as a read-a-long with the papers, we will not be going into a lot of detail but we will focus on the explaining the tricky minutia so that you can understand these papers more easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Village Panel Announcement</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/panel-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/posts/panel-announcement/</guid>
      <description>With DEF CON just two months away, we&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce two panels that will be held at AI Village this year! Here&amp;rsquo;s what we have planned for attendees so far:
(Responsible?) Offensive Machine Learning Panelists * @_delta_zero (Moderating) * @bodaceacat * @filar * @Straithe
Abstract: Cool evil hacks using machine learning are exploding in popularity. Not all ML abuse looks like Terminators, but also DeepFakes, political impersonation, and distracting autonomous cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max evil MLsec: why should you care?</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/max-evil-sjterp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/posts/max-evil-sjterp/</guid>
      <description>“Max evil” MLsec: why should you care? Originally posted on Medium - follow @sarajayneterp and like her article there
MLsec is the intersection of machine learning, artificial intelligence, deep learning and information security. It has an active community (see the MLsec project, Defcon’s AI Village and the CAMLIS conference) and a host of applications including the offensive ones outlined in “The Malicious Use of AI”.
One of the things we’ve been talking about is what it means to be ethical in this space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DEFCON China BETA 2018</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/events/china2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/events/china2018/</guid>
      <description>Time 12 May (Sat) 13 May (Sun)     1000 Village Exhibits Machine Learning as a Tool for Societal Exploitation: A Summary on the Current and Future State of Affairs - F1F1cin   1100 StuxNNet: Practical Live Memory Attacks on Machine Learning Systems - Raphael Norwitz Scrutinizing the Weakness and Strength of AI Systems - Dr Xinyu Xing, Dr Jimmy Su, Wenbo Guo   1200 Machine learning model hardening for fun and profit - Ariel Herbert-Voss StuxNNet: Practical Live Memory Attacks on Machine Learning Systems - Raphael Norwitz   1300 AI vs AI: Undercover the Billions of Black Market in e-Commerce - Dr Bin Zhao, Jin Yang Facilitating Postmortem Program Analysis with Deep Learning - Dr Xinyu Xing, Dr Jimmy Su, Wenbo Guo   1400 WORKSHOP: Pwning Machine Learning Systems - Clarence Chio Closing   1700 Village Exhibits -    Abstracts StuxNNet: Practical Live Memory Attacks on Machine Learning Systems slides, video 1, video 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dimensionality and Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/dimensionality-and-adversarial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/posts/dimensionality-and-adversarial/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to AI Village’s series on adversarial examples. This will focus on image classification attacks as they are simpler to work with and this series is meant to explain the attacks to hackers who have an interest in data science. The underlying principles are the same for attacks against malware/spam/security classifiers, though the implementation varies. This post focuses on the core reason why adversarial examples work, the high dimensional space our data occupies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the AI Village</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/about/</guid>
      <description>The AI Village is a community of hackers and data scientists working to educate the world on the use and abuse of artificial intelligence in security and privacy.
We are not sponsored by any one company, and it is our mission to maintain it as such as the community grows.
We have a presence at DEF CON, the world&amp;rsquo;s longest running and largest underground hacking conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/code-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/code-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>All delegates, speakers, sponsors and volunteers at AI Village are required to agree with the following code of conduct. Organizers will enforce this code throughout the event.
THE SHORT VERSION AI Village is dedicated to providing a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of gender, gender identity and expression, age, sexual orientation, disability, physical appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, religion (or lack thereof), or technology choices. We do not tolerate harassment of participants in any form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/sponsors/</guid>
      <description> Our sponsors make this all possible!
If you or your company is interested to be a sponsor, please get in touch with us.
Gold Sponsors  &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEAM</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/team/</guid>
      <description> Join us on our Slack channel (invitation)
CFP Review Board  @ak1010 @alexcpsec @filar @gradient_janitor @phtully @redragonvn @SaraTerp @Straithe @DavidFreeman  Core  @_delta_zero @adversariel @bwall @cchio @comath @filar @lysine_chan  Speakers DEFCON CHINA BETA (11-13 May 2018)  @adversariel @BinZhao @cchio @F1F1cin @raphael_norwitz @WenboGuo  Team  @antojosep007 @dth0m @eugeneteo @grue_ @J_L_Igyarto @rseymour  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>