<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aivillage.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AI Village Panel Announcement</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/panel-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/posts/panel-announcement/</guid>
      <description>With DEF CON just two months away, we&amp;rsquo;re excited to announce two panels that will be held at AI Village this year! Here&amp;rsquo;s what we have planned for attendees so far:
(Responsible?) Offensive Machine Learning Panelists * @_delta_zero (Moderating) * @bodaceacat * @filar * @Straithe
Abstract: Cool evil hacks using machine learning are exploding in popularity. Not all ML abuse looks like Terminators, but also DeepFakes, political impersonation, and distracting autonomous cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max evil MLsec: why should you care?</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/max-evil-sjterp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/posts/max-evil-sjterp/</guid>
      <description>“Max evil” MLsec: why should you care? Originally posted on Medium - follow @sarajayneterp and like her article there
MLsec is the intersection of machine learning, artificial intelligence, deep learning and information security. It has an active community (see the MLsec project, Defcon’s AI Village and the CAMLIS conference) and a host of applications including the offensive ones outlined in “The Malicious Use of AI”.
One of the things we’ve been talking about is what it means to be ethical in this space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dimensionality and Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://aivillage.org/posts/dimensionality-and-adversarial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aivillage.org/posts/dimensionality-and-adversarial/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to AI Village’s series on adversarial examples. This will focus on image classification attacks as they are simpler to work with and this series is meant to explain the attacks to hackers who have an interest in data science. The underlying principles are the same for attacks against malware/spam/security classifiers, though the implementation varies. This post focuses on the core reason why adversarial examples work, the high dimensional space our data occupies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>